PERSONAL DETAILS

Passionate young programmer with experience using C++, Game Engines, such as Unity or Unreal Engine 4 or Unity. Also experienced in 3D real-time rendering techniques.

Great problem-solving and team-working skills

Always aiming to improve, learning from the situation, and refining my skills day by day.

I am looking forward to join a team where I could share my passion about games, and continue learning.

In my spare time I really love working on personal projects or make small games.

EXPERIENCES

Gameplay Programmer at Rocket Banana

2017 - 2018

Esat end year project

A team we had when studying at Esat, developing a game and learning Unreal, and released on Steam.

My contributions are mainly related to gameplay.

- Main character movement
- Enemies behaviour and movement
- Main Menu Design & Implementation
- Implementation of local multiplayer

Programmer

2017 - 2018

Esat end year Game Engine

With the help of a partner, We developed a 3D Game Engine, using Open GL, capable of PBR rendering, deferred rendering, and lots of postprocesses, like SSAO, SSR, Bloom... To learn how a Game Engine performs.

Programmer

2019

Search for a star 2019

A small game I made, for the Search for a star 2019 contest.



Enrique Alemany Martínez

Graphics Programmer / Gameplay Programmer

Email: eagle2010@hotmail.es

Phone: <u>034 680769630</u>

WebPage: unyankee.github.io

Linkedin: <u>quique-alemany-</u> martinez-b837996b/

Github: unyankee

EDUCATION

BTEc Level 5 HND in Computing And Systems Development

ESAT

2015 - 2018

Graduated with Distinction

BSC(nonours) Computer Science for Games

Sheffield Hallam University 2018 - Expected 2019 Aiming To first

LANGUAGES

- English (C1 / 7 Band)
- Spanish (Native)

REFERENCES

Gustavo Aranda

- Programme Leader at ESAT
- garanda@esat.es

Juan Diego Alegre

- Project Manager at ESAT
- jd@esat.es

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

C

C++

C#

Swift

HTML

CSS

Java

JavaScript

GLSL

HLSL

ASM (ARM)

LUA

SOURCE CONTROL

GIT

Perforce

INTERESTS

Games

- Halo (saga)
- Halo Wars
- Warframe
- Hollow Knight
- Gears of War
- Flite Dangerous
- Terraria
- Dead Cells
- Borderlands
- Magicka
- Forza Horizon

Game Jams

Ludum Dare

Other

Music

Sports

Cvcling

<u>API'S</u>
OpenGL 3.X/4.X
DX11 (framework)
<u>ENGINES</u>
Unreal Engine 4
Unity
<u>IDE'S</u>
Visual Studio
XCode
Android Studio
<u>DEBUGGING</u>
Visual Studio
RenderDoc
Xcode
Android Studio
<u>OTHER</u>
Scrum
Constant Researching
Team working
Agile Software Development
<u>PLATFORMS</u>
Windows
Linux